SAMANTHA THICK

HTTP://SAMANTHATHICK.COM/

UNIVERSITY OF MICHIGAN SCHOOL OF INFORMATION

PROFILE

Senior in the School of Information following the Information Analysis track with a side focus in User Experience Design. Interested in new uses for technology in order to integrate business, society, and design to make information more accesible for everyday uses.

EXPERIENCE

HEAD SOFTBALL MANAGER | SEPT. 2017 - PRESENT University of MIchigan - Ann Arbor, MI

Collect team performance data using Flightscope, Rapsodo, HitTrax and Bats technology engaging with coaches by presenting pitching and hitting performance data for use in training and player development

Manage practice and game set-up providing support to coaches and team members along with assist in monitoring social media video and photography posts for Twitter, Instagram, and Facebook

CYBER SECURITY ENGINEER INTERN | JUN. 2020 - SEPT. 2020 Robert Bosch LLC, ETAS - Ann Arbor, MI

Assisted in setup of CAN and Ethernet fuzz testing runs and analyzed software failures using CAN data loggers along with internal tool software, functionality, stress, usability, and security testing

Developed and tested new user features, fuzz testing tools and solved bug fixes throughout internal application based on client feedback

Redesigned company dashboard and updated application documentation per client requests and commercialization of product and re-wrote CAN onboarding and documentation guidelines for future application users

IT DEVELOPMENT INTERN | JUN. 2019 - AUG. 2019 Cleveland Cavaliers - Cleveland, OH

Used API documentation to pull LeagueApps and Facebook Ad Data and created Python program for the Digital Media team to upload and organize team history projects

Created Amazon S3, AWS, buckets and data connections to help create a centralized data structure and make data usable for other departments by adapting to new data systems and problem solving to make it readable

Collaborated with a cross-functional team to help create and troubleshoot a Ticket Exchange App for customers

Trusted to learn an in depth understanding of Looker in order to advise the IT department on its uses for the company

PARKS ATTENDANT | JUN. 2017 - AUG. 2018 Oakland County Park and Recreation - Leonard, MI

Collected payments from clients and compiled cash transaction reports; Audited cash overages/shortages

Daily customer engagement when communicating with others to supervise park activities and private parties



STHICK@UMICH.EDU



810-358-8581



(in) IN/SAMANTHA-THICK

1313 S STATE STREET ANN ARBOR, MI 48104

EDUCATION & SKILLS

LAPEER HIGH SCHOOL GRADUATED 2017

UNIVERSITY GPA WITHIN MAJOR: 3.7

PYTHON

R

 \bigcirc ++

MATLAB

SQL

JAVASCRIPT

HTML5

CSS ADVANCED

EXCEL

LOOKER

ADOBE PHOTOSHOP

ADOBE ILLUSTRATOR

DJANGO

CAN

GIT

POWERSHELL

LEADERSHIP & GROUPS

U OF M SPORTS **ANALYTICS SOCIETY**

U OF M WOMEN IN SCIENCE AND ENGINEERING PROGRAM

LAPEER HIGH SCHOOL **OUTSTANDING SENIOR** AWARD